/* 
  DataFile.strings
  QuizApp

  Created by Damla Ã‡im on 15.03.2022.
  
*/

[{"id":7,"question":"How do we change permissions on files","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"chown","answer_b":"chmod","answer_c":"chattr","answer_d":"lsattr","answer_e":"We Can't change them","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"},{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":739,"question":"How to dump pod logs (stdout) in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl log my-pod","answer_b":"kubectl pod logs my-pod","answer_c":"kubectl logs my-pod","answer_d":"kubectl pods logs my-pod","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":723,"question":"Which command is used to create resources in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl create -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_b":"kubectl deploy -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_c":"kubectl apply -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_d":"kubectl fuse -f .\/my-manifest.yaml","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":709,"question":"Which special namespace is used for special purposes like bootstrapping a cluster?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"default","answer_b":"kube-public","answer_c":"kube-private","answer_d":"kube-default","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The kube-public namespace is created automatically and is readable by all users (including those not authenticated). This namespace is mostly reserved for cluster usage, in case that some resources should be visible and readable publicly throughout the whole cluster. The public aspect of this namespace is only a convention, not a requirement.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":682,"question":"Expand JFS in context of file system?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Journal File System","answer_b":"Journal Failing System","answer_c":"Journal File Service","answer_d":"Journal Failing Service","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":648,"question":"Which command can be used to determine file type by its content?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"file","answer_b":"ls \u2013l","answer_c":"type","answer_d":"None of the above.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":719,"question":"The kube-apiserver on Kubernetes master is designed to scale:","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Vertically","answer_b":"Horizontally","answer_c":"kube-apiserver is not used for scaling","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"The Kubernetes API server validates and configures data for the api objects which include pods, services, replicationcontrollers, and others. The API Server services REST operations and provides the frontend to the cluster\u2019s shared state through which all other components interact.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":1077,"question":"You are logged in as a normal user and you see a file with 444(-r--r--r--) permission. Can you delete it with the `rm` command?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"We can't be certain, it depends on the permissions of the parent folder","answer_b":"Yes, can delete it without a problem","answer_c":"No, we don't have the proper permissions","answer_d":"We can delete it only from the GUI but not from CLI.","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Linux"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":730,"question":"How to list PersistentVolumes sorted by capacity in Kubernetes?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl get pv --sort-by=.spec.capacity.volume","answer_b":"kubectl get pv --sort-by=.spec.capacity.storage","answer_c":"kubectl get pv --sort-by=.spec.capacity.memory","answer_d":"kubectl get pv --sort-by=.spec.capacity.space","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":718,"question":"Which command is used to create a Kubernetes service?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"kubectl set service","answer_b":"kubectl create service","answer_c":"kubectl deploy service","answer_d":"kubectl expose","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"}]
